<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Flushing Tour App</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="textview_about_flushing1">Flushing is a neighborhood in the north-central portion of the New York City borough of Queens. The neighborhood is the fourth-largest central business district in New York City. Downtown Flushing, a major commercial and retail area centered on the intersection of Main Street and Roosevelt Avenue, is the third-busiest intersection in New York City, behind Times Square and Herald Square.</string>
    <string name="wiki_link"><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Flushing,_Queens">Taken from Wikipedia</a></string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="home_tab">Home</string>
    <string name="food_shopping_tab">Food/Shopping</string>
    <string name="sightseeing_tab">SightSeeing</string>
    <string name="hotels_tab">Hotels</string>
    <string name="new_world_name">New World Mall</string>
    <string name="new_world_desc">Located in the heart of downtown Flushing and a short distance away from other heavily populated Queens neighborhoods, NWM stands to attract thousands of residents within the areas. The stunning three-story, cross-hatched window wall of clear glass on the exterior of the building has already received rave reviews from local community publications. This beautiful new mall is sure to enhance the appearance of the busiest block in Flushing and it reflects the company’s commitment to the community. The Mall expects to create over 1,000 new jobs and to promote social and economic awareness by hosting various community events and programs throughout the year.</string>
    <string name="new_world_link">https://www.newworldmallny.com/</string>
    <string name="new_world_address">136-20 Roosevelt Ave Flushing, NY 11354</string>
    <string name="new_world_phone">(718) 353-0551</string>
    <string name="sky_view_name">Sky View</string>
    <string name="sky_view_desc">THERE’S A RHYTHM TO THIS PART OF THE CITY. IT BEATS WITH EXCITEMENT LIKE A LOUD, RED DRUM. THE NOISE NEVER STOPS AND THE PEOPLE NEVER REST.\n</string>
    <string name="sky_view_desc2">And in the middle of it all is Skyview. We see you, we’re here for you, and our doors are open for whatever you need, whenever you need it.\n</string>
    <string name="sky_view_desc3">We feed you when you’re hungry, we’re in-step with your style, and we immerse you in the culture that makes this neighborhood so special. We’re a place to relax, to have fun, to indulge and to come together. You belong at The Shops at Skyview, because we know this is your place.</string>
    <string name="sky_view_link">https://theshopsatskyviewny.com</string>
    <string name="sky_view_address">40-24 College Point Boulevard Flushing, NY 11354</string>
    <string name="sky_view_phone">(718)460-2000</string>
    <string name="queenscrossing_name">Queens Crossing</string>
    <string name="queenscrossing_desc"><![CDATA[F&T Group is proud to present Queens Crossing, a state of the art mixed-use development in the heart of downtown Flushing, one of New York City’s most active and most diverse urban areas. Designed by world-renowned architects and engineers, the Thorton Tomasetti Group, Queens Crossing features a bold yet elegant architectural design that enhances its urban surroundings with a distinctive street presence. Behind its graceful curvilinear Façade, the building contains 110,000 sq. ft. of retail space, 37,000 sq. ft. entertainment and dining areas, full floor community facility, and 144,000 sq. ft. office condominiums, all served by 86,000 sq. ft. of valet parking. A visitor to this venue will discover specialty retail stores, both casual and fine dining options, and a large banquet hall at the lower levels of the building. Located on the fourth floor is Long Island Business Institute, a community college, and several medical offices. Floors five to eleven are professional offices, housing medical offices, lawyers, financial advisors, real estate and travel agencies. The top floor of Queens Crossing hosts the headquarters for the F&T Group.]]></string>
    <string name="queenscrossing_link">http://www.queenscrossing.com/</string>
    <string name="queenscrossing_address">136-17 39th Ave. Flushing, New York 11354</string>
    <string name="no_phone">N/A</string>
    <string name="fulton_name">One Fulton Square</string>
    <string name="fulton_desc">One Fulton Square offers a curated selection of authentic Asian eateries, including Chinese, Korean, Japanese, Malaysian and Taiwanese options. These bustling restaurants and bars are a vibrant addition to the nightlife of downtown Flushing and further advance the development of this flourishing neighborhood.</string>
    <string name="fulton_link">http://www.onefultonsquareflushing.com/</string>
    <string name="fulton_address">39-16 Prince Street Flushing, NY 11354</string>
    <string name="hyatt_name">Hyatt Place Flushing</string>
    <string name="hyatt_desc">Hyatt Place Flushing/LaGuardia Airport is an ultramodern hotel. It offers 168 guestrooms and one of the most unique rooftop spaces in the city—an outdoor garden, event spaces and restaurant and lounge with spectacular views of the Manhattan skyline.</string>
    <string name="hyatt_link">https://www.hyatt.com/en-US/hotel/new-york/hyatt-place-flushing-laguardia-airport/nyczf</string>
    <string name="hyatt_address">133-42 39th Avenue, Flushing, New York, United States, 11354</string>
    <string name="hyatt_phone">(718) 888-1234</string>
    <string name="parc_name">The Parc Hotel</string>
    <string name="parc_desc">Trips to New York City don’t have to be expensive. Take advantage of the specials and deals at The Parc Hotel to save big on your upcoming vacation or business trip. All of our hotel specials in Flushing include complimentary WiFi and daily buffet breakfast.</string>
    <string name="parc_link">https://www.theparchotel.com/</string>
    <string name="parc_address">3916 College Point Blvd Flushing, NY 11354</string>
    <string name="parc_phone">(718) 358-8897</string>
    <string name="marco_name">Marco Laguardia Hotel</string>
    <string name="marco_desc"><![CDATA[Marco LaGuardia Hotel & Suites is the ideal place to unwind amid the high-vibe buzz of New York City. Our central location in Flushing, Queens, puts you close to the action and serves as a perfect hub for your exploration of the city.]]></string>
    <string name="marco_link">https://www.marcolaguardiahotel.com/</string>
    <string name="marco_address">137-07 Northern Boulevard Flushing, New York 11354</string>
    <string name="marco_phone">(718) 445-3300</string>
    <string name="nybg_name">New York Botanical Garden</string>
    <string name="nybg_desc_l1">Queens Botanical Garden (QBG) is an urban oasis where people, plants, and cultures are celebrated through inspiring gardens, innovative educational programs, and real-world applications of environmental stewardship.\n</string>
    <string name="nybg_desc_l2">QBG is located on property owned by the City of New York, and its operation is made possible in part by public funds provided through the New York City Department of Cultural Affairs, Queens Borough President, the New York City Council, State elected officials, the New York State Department of Parks, Recreation and Historic Preservation, along with corporate, foundation, and individual supporters.</string>
    <string name="nybg_link">https://queensbotanical.org/</string>
    <string name="nybg_address">43-50 Main Street Flushing, NY 11355</string>
    <string name="nybg_phone">(718)886-3800</string>
    <string name="townhall_name">Flushing Town Hall</string>
    <string name="townhall_desc">The mission of Flushing Council on Culture and the Arts (FCCA) is to present multi-disciplinary global arts that engage and educate the global communities of Queens, New York and New York City, New York, in order to foster mutual appreciation. As advocates of arts equity since 1979, we support local, immigrant, national, and international artists, developing partnerships and collaborations that enhance our efforts. As a member of New York City’s Cultural Institutions Group (CIG), we serve as stewards of Flushing Town Hall, restoring, managing and programming the historic 1862 landmark on behalf of the City of New York. FCCA celebrates the history of Queens as the home of Jazz, by presenting the finest in Jazz performance. We are committed to arts education and hands-on learning, for the arts-curious, arts enthusiasts, and professional artists. We serve one of the most diverse communities in the world, and strive to uphold the legacy of inclusiveness that has defined our community since the Flushing Remonstrance of 1657</string>
    <string name="townhall_link">https://www.flushingtownhall.org</string>
    <string name="townhall_address">137-35 Northern Blvd Queens, NY 1135</string>
    <string name="townhall_phone">(718) 463-7700</string>
</resources>